Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/pratimap-309b0022 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals Healthcare Management Nursing

Pratima Prabhu Dhondya

CNO at xyz

United Arab Emirates

Summary

I believe in "what i think I will become" ,there are always better things coming for me.

"You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, "I have lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along." You must do the thing you think you cannot do.

"I BELIEVE IN MYSELF"

Experience

XYZ

Chief Nursing Officer February 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months) UAE

XYZ

Manager- Nursing & Education, LST trainer & Coordinator December 2013 - January 2018 (4 years 2 months)

United Arab Emirates

XYZ

Nursing Admin/Head Nurse January 2012 - January 2013 (1 year 1 month) Dubai

ZULEKHA HOSPITAL

Nurse Educator, Life Support Trainer , AHA training site Coordinator June 2009 - October 2011 (2 years 5 months)

Dubai

Alvas Education Foundation Registered Nurse, Assistant Lecturer

December 2003 - April 2006 (2 years 5 months)

Mangalore Area, India

Education

Manipal University MSN · (2006 - 2008)

AISECT UNIVERSITY

Doctor of Philosophy (PhD), Health/Health Care Administration/ Management · (2014 - 2019)

CARLTON ADVANCED MANAGEMENT ,USA AND MEC
CERTIFIED CORPORATE TRAINER AND FACILITATION, TRAINING AND
FACILITATION · (2012 - 2012)

Apollo Hospital

Post Graduate Diploma in Health Administration, Health/Health Care Administration/Management · (2010 - 2011)

AMERICAN HEART ASSOCIATION
BLS INSTRUCTOR (REGULARLY RENEWED), LIFE SUPPORT
TRAINING · (2009 - 2009)